<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>

  <name>Gone Joyful Traits</name>

  <author>gwen blanket knight</author>

    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
    </supportedVersions>
  <description>This mod adds 16 traits that affect how colonists enjoy the world around them.
This mod is in an early phase. i tested as extensively as I could so bug reports are valued.
used the buttons from https://opengameart.org/content/gui-buttons-0 as the background for the below images

 [h1]SPECIAL THANKS[/h1]
 [url=https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=49129.0] LoonyLadle[/url] for helping me get the rimworld c# coding environment setup
 [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/moloyHasArc/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100] moloy559[/url] for helping me get my code base started
 [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/eBlairGames/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100] eBlair[/url] for coding up the required mod to allow joys altered by traits
 [h1]LOAD ORDER![/h1]
 GWEN THOUGHT PATCH (near top of load order. i made it separate so the game wouldn't complain about doubled nullified fields)
 any mods that alter pawn thoughts such as psychology
 THIS (anywhere you'd normally put trait mods)
 [h1]SUPPORT THE MOD![/h1]
You can support the mod by commenting on balance, making bug reports, and offering suggestions. You can also click these buttons to push the mod closer to the front page of the workshop. This is the best method for discovery other than word of mouth.
[img=https://i.imgur.com/fVVaDCS.gif[/img]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/GwenLilyKnight/myworkshopfiles/]You can also follow my workshop page to see when a new mod is posted or check out my catalog[img]https://i.imgur.com/r1EtYC9.png[/img][/url]
[url=https://discord.gg/WJmGCzH]You can also join my discord server to receive live progress reports or give live feedback.[img]https://i.imgur.com/0oTSG7x.png[/img][/url]

[h1]TO DO[/h1]
GIT HUB LINK SOON AS I MAKE A REPOSITORY
ABILITY TO TOGGLE OFF UNWATNED TRAITS FROM APPEAERING
</description>

</ModMetaData>